(Leonard:)Have you guys heard
about this research team
(Leonard:)that's trying to transgenically
manipulate chicken DNA
(Leonard:)to create some sort
of chicken dinosaur?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I think that
sounds wonderful.
(Howard:)What? You're afraid
of both dinosaurs and chickens.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but tell me
(Sheldon:)a dinosaur
chicken salad sandwich
(Sheldon:)wouldn't hit the Mesozoic spot.
(Raj:)Hey, guys.
Hey.
Hello.
(Raj:)We still on for
tomorrow night?
(Leonard:)Yeah. I'm excited
to finally meet your girlfriend.
Yeah, oh, and
speaking of which.
(Sheldon:)According to a recent study
out of Oxford University,
(Sheldon:)when someone takes on
(Sheldon:)a new romantic
partner,
(Sheldon:)that person loses one
or two close friends.
(Howard:)Since when do you read
social science?
(Sheldon:)I go to the bathroom
like everybody else.
(Raj:)Why would I lose friends
(Raj:)just because I
started dating someone?
(Leonard:)Yeah, you didn't lose anyone
when you met Amy.
Yeah, well, no, the study
refers to romantic partners.
(Leonard:)Not the way I would
categorize the two of us.
(Raj:)You guys kiss and hold hands.
(Leonard:)I've seen him do it.
It's not romantic.
(Raj:)Look, I'm not the kind of guy
(Raj:)who drops his friends just
because he's in a relationship.
(Leonard:)What happens
if she doesn't like us?
(Raj:)Well, hey,
you're my dear friends.
(Raj:)You'll get a Christmas card
for a couple of years,
(Raj:)and then you're dead to me.